nec.edu 2006-12-21

# 

**New England College Privacy Policy**

This statement discloses the privacy practices of the New England College Web site. Our mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the principles of disclosure and informed consent. When you visit our Web site you can expect to be notified of: 

What information is gathered/tracked   
How the information is used   
Personal information

We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit us on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.   
If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet in order to register for a class or process an order, or to correspond with you   
\- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information.   
If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. 

**Information security and quality**

We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner. 

**Business relationships**

Our site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Cookies**

There are various technologies, including one called "cookies", which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some pages may use cookies or other technologies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
